Mohamed Ahmed Basyoni

Filmmaker

 \boxtimes

basyonifilmmaker@gmail.com



+966506843710

9

Riyadh – Saudi Arabia

Objective

Highly imaginative filmmaker with a solid seven years of experience making a variety of films for a variety of industries. Have a strong passion for creating independent films, but also have a knack for creating commercials, commercial productions, documentaries, and short films utilizing my knowledge of the latest camera, video, and audio equipment and editing software.

Experience

Per4Max Agency	JUN 2024 - Present
Creative Art Director Filmmaker	
Opacity-adv	JUN 2023 - JUN 2024
Video editing and Filmmaker	
• Vision Co. of Saudi Arabia	JUN 2022 - JUN 2023
Video editing and Videographer	
 Wasila Academy for Media Production 	Nov 2019 - Jun 2021
Founder, Cairo	
 Next Video Production 	Oct 2019 - Aug 2018
Videographer, Cairo	
Freelance videographer and editor	Oct 2018 - Aug 2016
Videographer, Cairo	_

Education

Bachelor of Survey engineering, KMA	Mar 2020
Egypt, Alexandria	

Certifications

Graphic design intern.	Oct 2022
National Telecommunication Institute (NTI)	
Score: 95%	
• 2D Animation: Walk Cycles.	JUL 2021
LinkedIn	
• DaVinci Resolve Fundamentals	NOV 2020
LinkedIn	
 Motion Graphic Design: Storyboards and Animatics 	Sep 2019
LinkedIn	
Motion Graphics Loops: 2 After Effects Techniques	Sep 2018
LinkedIn	
Fundamentals of Digital Marketing	Apr 2017

Personal details

<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Website</u>

Skills

Technical skills:

- ADOBE PREMIERE
- ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS
- ADOBE AUDITION
- ADOBE PHOTOSHOP
- DAVINCI RESOLVE
- ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR
- ADOBE LIGHTROOM
- RONIN STABILIZERS
- CMERAS (SONY-CANON-NIKON)

Interpersonal skills:

- Very good oral and written communication skills.
- Ability to work independently, as well as within a team of multidisciplinary professionals.
- Analytical and critical thinking skills.
- Ability to work with sophisticated technology.

Languages:

• Arabic: native

• English: B1

References

References are available upon request.